I'm actually sleeping over.
This is supposed to be my
big, big, big chance to win.
Today, I will lose.
The first one whose heart races loses?!
I'm staying over with the guy I like!
There's no way I can win!
My heart's never pounded
this hard in my life!
Who the hell came up with this game?!
Wakana-chan did say
she'd lend me her clothes.
I guess he's
bathing next...
Yukiya's clothes are here, too.
Yukiya.
Thanks for the change of clothes.
I Want to End This Love Game
Well?
Episode 7
My Childhood Friend Wants to Win
Do I look good?
W-Wait, that's mine!
I left Wakana's there, didn't I?
It was a bit small.
Let me guess...
Is it like I'm wearing
my boyfriend's shirt?
Did it make your heart skip a beat?
I'm in a boss fight.
Let me focus.
Never mind that!
You have a bigger boss fight
right in front of you!
Look at me!
What's your problem?!
Wakana, did you find the game yet?
Help me look for it, Onii!
There was a different game in the case!
Okay, I'm coming.
How can she even do that?!
How am I supposed to counter it?
That was so close!
We can play whatever
you're good at next.
All right, then...
Calpeace
You scared me!
What, was it a cockroach or something?
No, it's nothing.
I-I'm going to the bathroom.
Oh, okay.
I did it again.
And then like this, right?
Oh, I see.
I-I think I should head home now.
I'm getting hungry.
Oh, okay.
Bye-bye.
Thanks for having me.
It's just like that time.
All because I act so weird.
Hey, can I open this?
Sure.
Let's get some of the other ones, too.
Have some, Yukiya.
Jagabee
Rich Soy Sauce & Butter Flavor
Dammit...
She's smiling like none
of that bothered her.
Compared to her, I...
I said I wouldn't do
anything to upset her,
but all because I have that
type of stuff in my mind...
I'm so lame...
I'm so lame.
drowsy...
Wakana, get some sleep.
Miku-chan, wanna sleep in my room?
Don't.
Wakana's still a restless sleeper.
Are you?
You used to kick my face all the time.
I'll set up a futon in the
Japanese room like before.
There.
Okay, I'm going to my room.
Stop it, dummy.
You're going to stretch my clothes.
Wh-What?
You're just being shy, aren't you?
Does this mean I win?
Don't be dumb.
Stay a little longer.
I wanna talk for a bit.
Why is she...?
She has to have feelings for me, right?
How else could she
bring herself to do this?
Isn't that right?
You're usually still up
around this time.
Which is why I thought
I'd game in my own room.
Even though I'm here?
You can game together with me.
With you?
Together?
You've always been so stubborn.
I know you want to play with me.
You could just tell me
what you want to do.
I wouldn't really...
You...
You don't get it.
You don't know how I see you.
There's no way I could
tell you what I want to do.
Yeah, you're right.
Since you're here, we may
as well play that game.
We have the Love Game to play.
I'll play with you a little longer.
I Want to End This Love Game
No...
She isn't running.
You run, you lose.
You're the one who invited me
to play together.
I-I did, but I didn't mean like this.
I just didn't want to be neglected.
This... This is a bit...
A bit dirty.
Sorry.
I took it too far.
Yukiya...
Are you bored of the Love Game?
Wanna quit?
Why?
You seem, you know...
A bit distant.
I thought you might feel like you're
being put up to playing the Love Game.
Not really.
We cooked together like we used to today.
Dinner was really good.
And the league battle was fun.
In the lead!
Over here!
Nice!
But...
I'm troubling you.
If... If it's because
we're playing the Love Game,
that would suck.
Is this what she's been thinking about?
I've been having bad thoughts.
And I've been acting
awkward because of it.
But Miku...
I...
I'm glad we played the Love Game.
See...
You inspired me
to take on your challenge.
Like, I think you helped me
change a little.
Not just in my appearance.
M-Me, too.
I think this game helped me change a lot.
I'm thinking every day, all the time,
about how to make your heart race.
I've been...
I think it's about time
we tell each other.
But...
Now's not the time.
Even if I were to admit defeat,
and we started dating properly...
Miku's my princess,
but I'm not good enough for her.
I'm not the one who can
take her first place flag.
I don't deserve to be the reason
Miku makes those faces.
It's not like I can
be by her side forever.
I lack so much confidence
that I can't help but think that.
I can't be with her while
these thoughts are in my head.
But, even as pathetic as I am,
the Love Game changed me.
Without the Love Game, I never
would have thought to change.
I...
Skincare for guys
who are self-conscious
Rental Dresses
stare...
thump
Wanted so much for Miku to look at me.
And I worked for it.
I learned to confront my own feelings.
The Love Game changed me.
I was always crying, but since
I met Yukiya, I became cheerful.
Ever since I fell in love with him,
since I started playing the Love Game,
I learned to accept that I'm pretty.
So, what
do you think?
Did I take
your breath away?
At first, I was just playing
the game to kill time.
I started the game because
I wanted Yukiya's attention.
What does Miku like?
How does Yukiya like things flavored?
How does Miku like to dress?
What kind of things interest Yukiya?
She's always...
Koi-Kyun
He's always...
Miku's always...
Yukiya's always...
been on my mind.
It's the Love Game that
made me able to love someone.
It's what made me want to
change for someone I love.
Which is why...
We're still...
Then...
The first one to pull away loses.
You're probably going to be the first one to pull away anyway.
What?
That's some wishful thinking.
I could keep going.
So could I.
This is a piece of cake, loser.
Okay, we're staying like this
until the morning, then.
Your heart's racing.
No, it's not.
That's probably yours.
You're breathing so hard.
I can feel it against my head.
You're nervous, aren't you?
I have a ton of lung capacity.
I have to inhale and exhale
more than most people.
Stop sniffing!
One day, I'm going to...
I'm going to become good enough for him.
Until then, I'm not
letting the Love Game end.
Miku, get up!
Crap, Wakana's awake!
Already?!
I'll head to the living room.
Follow me later!
Huh?
Onii, you're awake.
Yeah, I couldn't get back to sleep.
That was close.
I thought I was going to die!
Yukiya ended up
detaching himself first.
I'm gonna go tease him.
Morning.
H-Hey.
M-Mhm.
fidget
I've seen this before
in manga
Wh-What's going on over there?
I've seen this vibe in manga before.
I've seen this before
in manga
Something must have happened!
I've seen this before
in manga
I thought they wouldn't
do anything with me around!
Ew, Onii!
Ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew
Ew, ew, ew, ew!
Why are you suddenly dissing me?!
Oh, right, sorry,
I was going to make breakfast.
Ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew ew
Here.
You made this?
Miso soup is easy enough.
Though, well, you should
still appreciate it.
Good for you.
Did you melt that miso good?
Quit treating me like a kid!
Breakfast, please.
Okay.
Morning, Yukiya.
That face...
Did your heart skip a beat
seeing my summer uniform?
And you must have been
stunned by my summer clothes.
I can smell your sweat.
Did that get you?
You say that,
but I bet you're clinging to me
because you want me to hug you again.
Well? Did that get your heart going?
Not really.
You're sweating.
So are you.
Hey,
aren't you going to be late?
You wasted time sticking to me,
and now we're late!
It's because you're being so slow!
We've grown up just a little.
And this is the beginning
of our unforgettable summer.
Next Time
My Childhood Friend and the Student Council President
Yukiya.
Yeah?
Do you know what the student
council president does?
Why do you ask?
The class rep is...
So the student council president
shows up in the next episode. Got it.
Next episode: "My Childhood Friend
and the Student Council President."